https://kurosbio.com/privacy-policy/

Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit. Totam officia reprehenderit eaque quos nobis nostrum, dolorum corrupti cumque nam quae atque itaque sunt iusto animi nihil fugiat sint quibusdam est.
ACCEPT
X
Where are you?
To give you the most accurate information about our products and what we can do for you, we need to direct you to the right site.
USA
Rest of world
Privacy Policy
Because we are committed to respecting the privacy of our web site visitors, this web site Privacy Policy describes the information we may collect from you during your visit to our site, how we may use it, and how we will protect the information which you may opt to provide. This policy explains the efforts to balance our business interests in collecting and using the information we receive from you with your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information that you share with us. Please note that by accessing and using this web site you automatically consent to us using any information provided by you in line with this policy.
Personally Identifiable Information
Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, phone number, e-mail address or any other information which might reasonably be used to identify you individually. Kuros collects personally identifiable information from web site visitors only when it is voluntarily provided. Kuros will not otherwise collect this information from you on our web site.
At those portions of our web site where we provide you with the option to input personally identifiable information, we notify you of the uses we intend to make of that information in any given instance. When Kuros receives personally identifiable information, we may use it for reasonable business purposes, just as non-Internet businesses do. For example, we may use this information to contact you, via e-mail or regular mail, to provide you with information we believe may be of interest. It might also be used for compiling data and analyses to understand and serve our customers’ needs. Data is also compiled to evaluate the use and utility of the services we provide on-line. Your information may be transferred for processing and use to Kuros facilities in other countries and regions of the world. Personally identifiable information will not be sold or rented by Kuros unless the user is first notified and expressly consents to such transfer.
Collective/Aggregate Data
The Kuros web site may also collect information from you that is not personally identifiable. For example, we might track information about the date and time visitors access our site, the type of web browser they used, and the web site from which they connected to our site. Our web sites collect this information by depositing certain bits of information called “cookies” in a visitor’s computer. This technology does not collect an individual visitor’s personally identifiable information. Rather, this information is collected in an aggregate form. The cookies can tell us how and when pages in a web site were visited and by how many people. This aggregate information will enable us to improve our web sites to serve and inform you better. It also may allow you to shortcut access to points of interest on our web site when you re-enter our system. Attaching this device to your system has no effect on how it performs.
Links To Other Sites
As a resource to our visitors, Kuros may provide links to other web sites. We try to carefully choose web sites, which we believe are useful and meet our high standards for the accuracy and utility of information. However, because web site design and content can change so quickly, we cannot guarantee the standards of every web site to which we link. Likewise, we are not responsible for the content of any non-Kuros site. We also cannot guarantee the privacy policies of these other sites and suggest you check the privacy policies of those sites directly.
Choice
If you wish to stop receiving any e-mails or other communications from Kuros which may besent to you in the future based on your request for this information, or if you have submitted personally identifiable information through a Kuros web site and would like to have that information deleted from our records, please notify us via the contact form on the this site. Your wishes in these matters will be honoured.
Accuracy
Kuros will make every effort to maintain the accuracy and confidentiality of any personal information you supply to us. If you wish to make additions or other corrections to the information that you have sent in, please transmit it to us via the contact form on the site.
Security
All information transmitted to this Kuros web site is secure to the extent possible using existing technology. Unauthorised third parties should not be able to access it during transmission. We will store the information that you share with us securely and will take appropriate steps to protect it from unauthorised access or disclosure. While no security steps can offer 100 percent protection, we utilise state-of-the-art technology and systems to prevent unauthorised access to the information we hold. We will limit access to this information to those Kuros personnel with a need to know. We educate our staff about their duty to protect your privacy.
Children
Kuros does not intentionally collect or retain personally identifiable information about children who are younger than 18 years of age. If your child may have submitted information to us without indicating their actual age, and you would like it removed, please advise us through the contact form on the site, and we will delete it immediately.
Changes
Any changes to this privacy policy will be communicated promptly at this location. Please check the privacy policy periodically to review any changes that may have been made.
We use cookies to help our website work and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our analytics partner. Your continued use of our site implies you agree to this.
ACCEPT
X
